https://www.extronics.com/privacy-policy/

ProductsWirelessAccess Point EnclosuresiWAP107 Zone 1/Div 1 wireless systemiWAP XN3 Zone 2/Div 2 wireless systemiWAP202 Zone 2 AP systemPOE/Ethernet extenderiSOLATE TechnologyiSOLATE501 RF isolatoriSOLATE-CT connector transitAntennasiANT216 dual band Wi-Fi antennaiANT212 compact Wi-Fi antennaiANT221 2×2 MIMO antennaiANT218 3×3 MIMO antennaiANT214 Wi-Fi antennaiANT213 Wi-Fi & GSM antennaiANT215 low profile Wi-Fi antennaiANT217 circular UHF antennaiANT200 omnidirectional antennaiANT100 Zone 1 Wi-Fi & GSM antennaiANT101 Zone 1 Wi-Fi antennaReal Time Location Systems (RTLS)TagsiTAG X30 Worker Location Tag with Hybrid TechnologyiTAG100 Zone 1 RFID tagT2 Wi-Fi RFID TagTGUARD tag protectorT2-EB extended battery tagT2L Multi-LED tagT2s TagT3 advanced tagT3i integration tagT5 sensor tagT12 Bi-Directional Asset TagT14 Bi-Directional Worker BadgeExcitersiCITE101 Zone 1 tag exciterEX5200 tag exciterEX3220 tag exciterEX5210R outdoor tag exciterHardware ManagementTag & Exciter Detector (TED)Hardware ManagerEvaluation & DevelopmentEvaluation Development KitSoftwareMobileView visibility platformInstant Notifier alert softwareTrainingMobileView RTLS Technical TrainingMaintenance & SupportMaintenance & SupportAuto ID Asset ManagementPassive RFIDiRFID500 Zone 0 Bluetooth RFID readeriRFID101 Zone 1 fixed universal RFID readeriTAG500 passive RFID tag rangeBarcode ScannersiSCAN101 Zone 1 cabled barcode scanneriSCAN211 Zone 1 Bluetooth barcode scanneriSCAN2012D Zone 1 Bluetooth barcode scanneriSCAN301 1D and 2D fixed readerBarcode Scanner Power SuppliesiSCANPS Zone 1 power supplyEngineeringEngineering ServicesEngineeringUninterruptible Power SuppliesiUPS101 Zone 1 UPSiUPS200 Zone 2 UPSBatteriesiBATT5xx Zone 1 universal battery systemiBATT100 Zone 1 battery systemBKEx battery boxiCAM502 Zone 0 handheld cameraSolutionsWireless NetworkingWorker SafetyAsset TrackingCondition MonitoringAboutAbout ExtronicsIndustries we serveLeadership TeamCareersQuality and ComplianceResourcesTestimonialsSupportNews and EventsBlogPartnersPartnersBecome a PartnerContact Us Privacy PolicyIntegrity is one of our core values, which means we look after your privacy. We’ve updated our privacy policy to reassure you that we’re fully compliant with the EU’s General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), effective as of 25th May 2018.Using our websiteWe use Google Analytics to collect standard web log information about the audience we’re reaching and behaviour of visitors, such as number of people viewing a particular page. This information is processed anonymously; we don’t identify anyone. We use it to improve our website and give you a better browsing experience. We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our website.Personal information (such as your name and email address) submitted through our contact us page or chat function may be used to provide you with information you’ve requested, send information we think may be of interest to you, promote services we think you may find helpful, and meet any legal requirements we have towards you.Sharing personal informationWe never sell your personal information to any third party.Where appropriate, we may share your data with certified Sales Partners and VARs in order to give you information you have requested or may find of interest, or to provide you with improved customer service.We post customer testimonials on our website, which may include personal information. We obtain consent via email or telephone first.Your data protection rightsUnder GDPR, you have the right to request access, updating, or deletion of your personal information; to object to or restrict our processing of your data; and to request data portability. To exercise any of these rights, please contact info@extronics.com.If you do not wish to receive marketing information from us, you may unsubscribe at any time using the ‘unsubscribe’ link at the bottom of each email.Use of cookiesCookies are small text files on your hard drive, used for keeping track of settings or data for a particular web site. Because the servers that receive your requests for web pages have no way of knowing specifically who is making a request, they have no way of storing settings for specific users or changing the page they send based on choices a user has made on another page.Cookies solve this problem by saving settings on your (the user’s) system. When your browser requests a page, it sends the settings that apply to that page along with the request. Because your browser will only send the settings back to the server that originally created them, cookies are a very secure way of maintaining data that is specific to a particular user.Cookies can also be used to help save and retrieve usernames used on our site and other preferences. This is done for convenience and means that you do not have to re-enter this information on every visit. Extronics Ltd does not and cannot use cookies to retrieve personal information about you from your computer unless such information was knowingly and willingly provided by you.Website content and limitation of liabilityYou may not reproduce or distribute any information or image from this website, in whole or in part, without the prior written permission of Extronics Ltd. Requests for permission of use should be sent via email to info@Extronics.com and should include your name, address, a description of the information which you would like to distribute, and the intended recipients of that information.The information, data, and images included in this web site have been compiled by Extronics Ltd and are subject to change without notice. Extronics Ltd makes no warranties or representations, whatsoever, about the quality, content, completeness or adequacy of such information, data or images. Extronics Ltd shall not be liable for any special, incidental or consequential damages, including, without limitation, lost revenues, lost profits or loss of prospective economic advantage, resulting from the use or misuse of any file in this website or the information, data or images herein.It is your responsibility to take precautions to ensure that whichever web page you select for viewing is free from viruses and other items of a destructive nature. It is your responsibility to ensure that any page or web site which you select for viewing is free from content which you may deem inappropriate.Except where specifically stated on this website, to the fullest extent permitted by law, neither Extronics Ltd nor any of its members, directors, employees or other representatives shall be liable for damages arising out of or in connection with the use of this web site or the information, services or products included on this site. This is a comprehensive limitation of liability which applies to all damages of any kind, including (without limitation) compensatory, direct, indirect or consequential damages, loss of data, income or profit, loss of or damage to property and claims of third parties.
By continuing to use the site, you agree to the use of cookies. We use cookies to enhance you experience. more information AcceptThe cookie settings on this website are set to "allow cookies" to give you the best browsing experience possible. If you continue to use this website without changing your cookie settings or you click "Accept" below then you are consenting to this.Close
